A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Near & Middle East, Record Group 3, Series 9 FA1777
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Joint Committee on the Comparative Study of Muslim Societies, 1984-1995; 2; 6.93 Cubic Feet 17 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
  - Dissertation Workshop - Ferrie, Jean-Noel, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 513)
  - Dissertation Workshop Applications, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 514)
  - Postdoctorate Grant Requests, 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 515)
  - Tangier Dissertation Workshop, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 516-517)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Villasante, Mariella, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 518)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Toohey, Aileen, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 519)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Zarinebaf-Shahr, Fariba (Withdrew 4/90), 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 520)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Guyomarch, Claude (Withdrew), 1990 (Box 54, Folder 521)
  - Dissertation Workshop - El-Hibri, Tayeb, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 522)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Devji, Faisal, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 523)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Ghalmi, Myriam, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 524)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Alikberov, Alikber K., 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 525)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Hutson, Alaine, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 526)
  - Dissertation Workshop 1990 - Mukarram, Ahmed, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 527)
  - Dissertation Workshop 1990 - Popenoe, Rebecca, 1989-1990 (Box 54, Folder 528)
  - General Correspondence, Memos, and Notes, 1984-1988 (Box 54, Folder 529-532, Box 55, Folder 533-535)
  - Paris Minorities Workshop, 1985-1987 (Box 55, Folder 536-537)
  - Dissertation Workshop - Istanbul, 1988 June (Box 55, Folder 538, Box 56, Folder 539)
  - Committee Correspondence, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 540-541)